and we'll be good to go.
>> Okay. Thank you.
Hey Keonte, how are we doing?
>> I'm doing good.
>> Excellent, man. Welcome to Tampa. We're
excited to have you. I'm going to bring
our local media in here in just a second
and then we're just going to have a
quick little session with you. All
right.
>> All right. Perfect.
>> Thank you.
chairs. I'm like standing up from
another chair. I didn't realize this
chair. No, we're chairs.
>> All right, we can go ahead and get
started. Rick, I'll let you lead us off.
That works for you.
>> Works for just fine. Congratulations,
Kante. Um, I guess you're familiar with
at least, uh, one rookie here in Tampa
Bay. Just your thoughts about joining
Ruben and, uh, the opportunity to come
up here and play together again.
>> Yeah, man. Definitely, uh, you know,
that is going to be, you know, super
exciting to get that that opportunity
again. You know, just, you know, as the
season went on, you know, just, you
know, starting to compete with Bane, you
know, having little locker room talks
like, man, I I want I want true tackles,
you know, kind of like racing to the
ball. So, it's just fun to, you know, be
around somebody that plays the game the
way Ruben does. So, I'm definitely
excited about that. been talked about as
a physical downhill aggressive against
the run type of player. Just talk about
your strengths in that area, where they
come from and and what you think you can
bring to the Bucks in that area.
>> Yeah, ultimately just, you know, the
want to. I feel like, you know, I try to
pride myself on being an old school cat,
you know, play the game like at old
school, flying around, you know, being
able to, you know, put my stick, not
being afraid to stick my nose, you know,
in anything and, you know, kind of just,
you know, playing fast. And I feel like,
you know, that that attribute for that,
you know, kind of helps the defense at
times, too. By me being able to just,
you know, fly around and and being able
to race things before they get started.
>> Kante, I feel like there's two things
that Todd Bulls loves on defense, and
it's smart and versatility. How much
interaction have you had with your
coaches and how well do you think you
fit into this defense? Yeah, I
definitely, man. This is that definitely
a scheme that was on, you know, on on my
as far as where I felt like I would fit
at, you know, this scheme that, you
know, is being ran is just, you know,
it's amazing, you know, what he what he
does on defense as far as, you know,
show the versatility, but of the
defensive backs also. And I'm just super
excited to get there and get to work,
man. I'm super excited.
>> Speaking of the scheme, it it asked slot
corners to uh blitz a lot. You actually
led all cornerbacks in the NCAA last
year with 20 pressures, few sacks. Can
you talk about what it is about your
instincts when it comes to blitzing that
allows you to be so successful?
>> Yeah, I think you got to shout out Ruben
Bane there. You know, us being on the
same side, you know, you got to kind of
worry about him a little bit. So that
allowed me to, you know, kind of be
freed up. So, you know, we worked with
each other and that's why this is so
special to me and so special to him
because, you know, we've we built
something already, you know, kind of,
you know, so just getting to build on
that. But then ultimately I would just
say you know um understanding that you
know at the end of the day when you get
sent on a blitz you know you're kind of
your brothers are I play defensive back
so you know I understand how it is when
you're you know you're blitzing and you
know you're waiting somebody better get
home. You know what I'm saying? So you
know I just take that into mind that I
got my brothers back there and you know
when I get that call to go you know I
take that you know with me on the way.
>> Outside of Ruben do you have any other
connections to the Buccaneers?
>> Uh no.
You've mentioned in pre-draft interviews
that you're willing to play anywhere on
the field at the next level. Uh where do
you kind of envision yourself on the
field in the NFL and maybe get an idea
of where the Buccaneers might want to
put you uh in this year beyond?
>> Yeah, like I said, you know, and spoke
on before, you know, I feel like, you
know, I pride myself on being a
defensive back and um definitely, you
know, have this chip building up on my
shoulder that I was already there. It's,
you know, it's much bigger. So, the fact
that, you know, wherever it's going to
be for the team, you know, whatever I
can do for the city of Tampa Bay and,
you know, get that place rocking, um is
something I'm willing to do. Keonte,
talk a little bit more about that chip
on your shoulder. You started off at Jo
and you kind of had to b your time
before having a platform year with the
Hurricanes.
>> Yeah, I would just say ultimately ups
and downs, you know, everything that
made me who I am today. Um, ultimately,
you know, learning lessons and and
different things like that, but then
ultimately, you know, I feel like I'
I've handled adversity well. You know,
even situations like I'm in now. You
know, I feel like, you know, at the end
of the day, it's just time to, you know,
answer that call again on if he'll do it
again. And I just feel like I'm, you
know, super confident in my ability to
handle adversity situations. So, I feel
like I'm I'm real comfortable right
here.
>> Ky, it looked like an amazing moment
there when you got the news to see the
pictures. Just the joy all around you.
You're you're home in South Carolina. Is
that right?
>> I'm in San Diego. Yes.
>> Oh, San Diego. I'm sorry.
>> Oh, yes. Yeah. I would just say
ultimately, you know, like, man, I
worked really hard. you know, a lot of
time being put into this, a lot of ups
and downs, like I said, and and to
finally get that call, man, I don't
think I could have grabbed the phone any
faster. I just, you know, super excited.
Um, and then to ultimately hear Tampa
Bay and, you know, to start going down
that list like, man, Ruben's there and
the scheme and, you know, the city in
general is just I'm super excited to to
get there and just start working.
>> Yay, have you spoken with Ruben yet?
What was his reaction if y'all have?
>> Yeah, he called me. We talked, you know,
he he was super excited for me. Um he's
actually, you know, down there. So, you
know, he he he stepped out of the room.
They told him that it was going down and
he stepped out and made the call to me
and, you know, I talked to him and we're
super excited to get, you know, to get
back to working together.
>> Wait, he made the call from the draft
room?
>> No, no, no. He called he was there at at
brunch and he stepped away and called
and called me.
>> You you talked to the GM and the coach
before you talked to to Bane?
>> Yes.
>> Okay. So, I thought he might have broke
the news to you.
>> No, no, no, no, no. Did you pitch him on
on on Wesley while you were on the phone
with him and trying to get
>> Yeah. Yeah. Well, the the talk was he
said he's he's trying he's trying to get
he's trying to get some Hurricanes down
that way. So, we'll see what how the
draft plays out.
>> What What's your message to Bucks fans
who are watching this right now? What
kind of player are they getting? What
kind of person are they getting? What
are you going to bring to the Bucks this
season?
>> Yeah, a straight dog, man. A player
that, you know, doesn't need anything
but an opportunity. And at the end of
the day, that's what I have now and I'm
looking forward to taking full advantage
of it.
>> All right. Appreciate it.
>> Thank you very much. Congratulations,
man.
>> I appreciate it. It was so nice to meet
you. I can't wait to start working with
you guys. I appreciate it.
>> Thanks very much.
>> Thank you.